Guide to the Reginald Sellman negatives, 1911-1935
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- Reginald Sellman negatives, 1911-1935, (3 boxes)
  - Sunset on Elk, in front of camp, 1932 Aug. 18 (Box 3, Image 879)
  - Bedie and R.O.S. in boat, in front of camp, 1932 Aug. 18 (Box 3, Image 880)
  - Across Elk, early morning, 1932 Aug. 19 (Box 3, Image 881)
  - Bedie, Grape Vine Cove, 1932 Aug. 22 (Box 3, Image 882)
  - Bedie, Grape Vine Cove, picking stones, 1932 Aug. 22 (Box 3, Image 883)
  - Up Cabin John's Creek, 1932 Aug. 22 (Box 3, Image 884)
  - Camp from Elk River, 1932 Aug. 22 (Box 3, Image 885)
  - Camp from Elk River, 1932 Aug. 22 (Box 3, Image 886)
  - Back of cottage, Bruce in swing, 1932 Aug. 23 (Box 3, Image 887)
  - Cabin John's Creek, 1932 Aug. 24 (Box 3, Image 888)
  - Marsh up Cabin John's Creek, 1932 Aug. 24 (Box 3, Image 889)
  - Bruce in boat, Leckler's Beach, 1932 Aug. 24 (Box 3, Image 890)
  - Fords Point from west, 1932 Aug. 24 (Box 3, Image 891)
  - R.O.S. in Bohemia Cove, 1932 Aug. 25 (Box 3, Image 892)
  - Bruce in Bohemia Cove, 1932 Aug. 25 (Box 3, Image 893)
  - Cove from Bohemia River, 1932 Aug. 25 (Box 3, Image 894)
  - Fords Point from near Ducking Point, 1932 Aug. 25 (Box 3, Image 895)
  - Across Elk from Frazer's porch, 1932 Aug. 25 (Box 3, Image 896)
  - Turkey Point from Frazer's porch, 1932 Aug. 25 (Box 3, Image 897)
  - Elk River from Frazer's lawn, 1932 Sept. 4 (Box 3, Image 898)
  - Elk River from Frazer's porch, 1932 Sept. 4 (Box 3, Image 899)
  - Turkey Point from Frazer's lawn, 1932 Sept. 4 (Box 3, Image 900)
  - Turkey Point from Frazer's lawn, 1932 Sept. 4 (Box 3, Image 901)
  - Frazer house from lawn, 1932 Sept. 4 (Box 3, Image 902)
  - Frazer house from lawn, 1932 Sept. 4 (Box 3, Image 903)
  - Susie's grave in Mount [Mound?] View cemetery, 1935 May 9 (Box 3, Image 904)
    Initials on the monument read "S.F.S." There are no visible dates.
  - Susie's monument, 1935 May 9 (Box 3, Image 905)
  - Us by cedar tree, Sue in room, Ford's Landing, [cypress?], 1935 May 14 (Box 3, Image 906)
    Composite image of photographs.
  - Sue and M.O.S., Sue in room, Ford's Landing, [cypress?], 1935 May 14 (Box 3, Image 907)
  - Sue and M.O.S., us by cedar tree, Ford's Landing, [cypress?], 1935 May 14 (Box 3, Image 908)
  - Susie Ford, my darling, copy of 390, 1935 May 14 (Box 3, Image 909)
    Image of photo of Susie in oval frame, with large book lying flat in foreground.
  - Susie Ford, my darling, copy of 390, 1935 May 14 (Box 3, Image 910)
  - Susie Ford, copy, 1935 May 14 (Box 3, Image 911)
    Image of several photos of Susie in a rectangular frame, with large book lying flat in foreground.